Guide to the Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society Papers 1835-1980 (Bulk 1840-1970) MS 74
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Papers
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, requests for letters of dismission, 1913-1914 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, new member lists, 1905-1916 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, new member lists, 1916-1920 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, new member lists, 1920-1922 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, new member lists, 1920-1937 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters from members requesting transfer, 1927-1928 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters from members requesting transfer, 1928-1930 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters from members requesting transfer, 1930-1934 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters from members requesting transfer, 1927-1939 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4859-#5062, 1912-1918 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5645-#6151, 1912-1918 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5276-#5471, 1912-1918 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #4859-#5642, 1912-1918 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5645-#5760, 1919-1923 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5762-#5856, 1919-1923 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5938-#6023, 1919-1923 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters received, #5645-#6151, 1919-1923 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1914-1922 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1914-1922 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1914-1922 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1914-1922 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1926-1927 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1921, 1926-1939 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1926-1930 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, letters of dismission, 1931-1934 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership correspondence, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership information, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1930 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1931 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1932 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1933 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1934 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1935 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1936 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1937 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, membership cards, filed 1938 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1930 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1931 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1932 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1933 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1934 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1935 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1936 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1937 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, members file cards, filed 1938 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Letter from Reverend J.P. Thompson to BroTab Society, 1853 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Reverend J.P. Thompson: correspondence with American and Foreign Christian Union, 1857 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Letters from Reverend J.P. Thompson, 1865-1878 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Reverend J.P. Thompson's resignation, 1871 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Call to Reverend W.M. Taylor, 1871 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Documents related to the call and installation of Reverend W.M. Taylor, 1871-1872 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Reverend W.M. Taylor's house, 1872-1873 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Letters: Reverend W.M. Taylor and Dakota Indian Mission, 1875 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Reverend W.M. Taylor, 1872-1890 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - W.M. Taylor, "The Rosebuds", [1903] (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - "William Mackergo Taylor", 1895 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Memories of BroTab, regarding 1851-1852 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Charles E. Jefferson: Installation, 1898 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Charles E. Jefferson: Installation, 1898 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Letters: Charles E. Jefferson, 1904-1930 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Charles E. Jefferson: Printed Materials, 1898-1923 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Charles E. Jefferson, Articles by, 1906-1960 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Charles E. Jefferson, Articles by, 1906-1930 February (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Charles E. Jefferson, resignation, 1930 August 29 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Allan Knight Chalmers: church letters, 1934-1940 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Allan Knight Chalmers: correspondence, 1938-1967 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Allan Knight Chalmers: newspaper clippings, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Albert J. Penner, correspondence, 1950-1958 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Albert J. Penner, 1949-1959 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Lawrence L. Durgin, [1969] (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Funeral Expense Journal, 1879-1882 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Council for Ordination, 1881 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Choir, 1886 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Endowed Bed Certificates, 1888-1904, [1952] (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Endowed Hospital Bed, 1908 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Sunday School. Letter from Knoxville, Tennessee, 1889 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Sunday School Treasurer's Report, 1890 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Trustees, 1890-1897 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Miscellaneous Treasurer's documents, 1890-1897 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Reverend W.M. Taylor: resignation, 1892 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Reverend Henry A. Stimson, 1893 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, draft: Confession of Faith Covenant, 1893 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, pews: rentals and policies, 1896-1899 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, seating plan of auditorium, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, newspaper clippings, 1898-1901 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Call to Reverend Charles E. Jefferson, 1898 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Reverend Charles E. Jefferson: Letter to C.B. Knevals, 1898 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Treasurer's Vouchers (60th Anniversary Fund), 1901-1902 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, estimated expenses (Trustees), 1901-1905 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, subscriptions, 1901 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Building Committee, 1902 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, general building specifications, 1902 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Congregational Pastors' Brotherhood, 1903 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Charles R. Seymour, 1904 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, dedication expenses, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Baptismal records, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Chinese Sunday School, 1896-1917 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Observances for Ushers, 1913 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Baptisms, 1893-1922 (Box 64)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Dismissions, 1893-1913 (Box 64)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Deaths, 1893-1911 (Box 64)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Discipline, 1894-1910 (Box 64)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Finance Committee, 1902-1907 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, bills, 1902-1903 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, bills, 1902-1903 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, bills, 1903-1904 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, New York Congregational Home for the Aged, 1906-1916 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Systematic Benevolence, 1910-1911 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Annual Reports, Board of Trustees, 1913-1924 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Lenten Class, 1912-1913 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Church Dinners, 1913 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, on Church membership, 1913, 1917 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, missionaries, 1915-1917 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Special Trust Fund receipts, 1918 November 1-1919 October 31 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, miscellanies of other churches, 1903-1969 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Revisions of the Creed, 1920-1921 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Committee of Fifteen, Jefferson Academy Committee, 1927-1940 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Committee Reports, 1920-1926 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Tidings, 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Report: Missionary Committee, 1927 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Committee on Pilgrim Hall, 1929 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Committee on Revision of Rules, [1930] (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Deacons, 1931-1932 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, proposed budget, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Church Committee, 1931-1933 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence A-J, 1931 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence K-Z, 1931 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence A-F, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence G-L, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence M-P, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Correspondence P-Z, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, "A Spirit Propelled by Divine Motion...", 1940 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Annual Meetings: Announcements, 1940-1946 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Exhibition Labels, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, investment display charts, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, summary of investments, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, a survey of BroTab, 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, BroTab Church Budget, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, miscellaneous papers, [1903-1974] (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Documents of Amalgamation, 1947 January 29 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, certificate of name change from Society to Church, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Constitution and By-Laws, 1947-1956 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Secretary to Board of Trustees, 1955-1961 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Secretary to Board of Trustees, 1957-1961 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Secretary to Board of Trustees, 1962-1964 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Annual Report to the Congregation, 1966, 1969, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Board of Deacons, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Board of Deacons: Action Summary, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Board of Deacons, 1970-1974 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, Board of Trustees, 1969-1973 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church, annual meeting, 1970-1976 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, inventory and appraisal, 1961 (Box 67)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, letter offering to purchase property, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, inventory: Church School, [1961] (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, disposition of church property to mission churches, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, "When a Protestant Congregation Moves into a Roman Catholic Church", 1969 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, St. Paul the Apostle, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, New Space, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, church recommendations, Alex Sareyan, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, proposal of merger between Broadway United Church and United Church of Christ, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, church committees, 1964-1969 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, consultation on program, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Interparish Council, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Church Council, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Church Council, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Church Council, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Nurture of the Congregation Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Nurture of the Congregation Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Education Task Force, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, survey: State of the Church, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, membership forms, undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Congregational Church and Broadway Church of Christ, Broadway United Christ Church seeks a new home, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, reports to state registrar, 1920-1928 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, insurance policies, 1935-1968 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, financial documents, 1939-1970 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, Finance Committee actions, 1956-1960 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, non-profit status, 1940, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, Church Extension Endowment Fund, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, Anna L. White estate, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, Frandian Associates, 1970-1986 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, standpipe inspections, 1959-1968 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, payroll budgets, 1959-1965 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, personnel, 1936-1958 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway Congregational Church, personnel, 1957-1961 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, personnel, 1958-1968 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, personnel, 1961-1967 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, excerpts regarding extension work, [1950] (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, social service project, West 56th Street, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Challenge for the BroTab Church: a survey from "Hell's Kitchen to San Juan Hill", 1952 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Religious Education Committee: counseling services, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Christian Endeavor Committee, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Resolutions, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, group ministry proposal, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Chaplaincy, 1962-1968 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, W.F. Dingley: Review of Endowment History lecture, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, W.F. Dingley, "Recollections of 46 Years at Broadway Church", 1967 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, letters to companies, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, activities for the week, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, newspaper clippings, 1963, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Corporate Meeting Dinner, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, "Riot" (theater production), 1968 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Church School Education, 1957-1969 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Church School, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Children's Center for the Arts (proposal), 1969 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, foundation proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Consultation on Pastoral Ministry (report), 1971 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, retreats, 1970 September 26, 1971 June 5 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, "Regathering", 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, Union Theological Seminary fieldwork at Broadway United Congregational Church, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, students-in care, 1971-1974 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Church and Broadway United Congregational Church, Broadway United Church of Christ, "Last names grouped by individual letter", undated (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1963-1979 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Ecumenical Mission Committee, 1970-1971, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Homeland and Ecumenical Ministries, 1967-1974 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Funding the Mission in New York City, Leland E. Gartrell, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee (1), 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee (2), 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Mission of the Church Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, "ACM - An Apparition of Christian Mission", 1970 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, "The New Tidings, Practice of Mission at BUCC", 1973 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Christian World Mission, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Poems by Kuangchi Chang, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Benevolence, 1975-1980 (Box 72, Folder 8)